Guide to the American Planning Association records, 1925-2015.
American Planning Association records,
- APA Divisions
  - Indigenous Planning Division, APA
    - University of New Mexico Library Repository, 2005 (Box 144, Folder 46)
    - Banking Issues, 2006 (Box 144, Folder 47)
    - Newsletters, 2005-2007 (Box 144, Folder 48)
    - Alaska APA Conference, 2007 (Box 144, Folder 49)
    - Archives, Financial documents, 2007-2011 (Box 144, Folder 50)
  - Housing and Community Development Division, APA
    Name changed from 'Human Services and Social Planning Services Division', probably c. 2001
    - Correspondence, 1996 (Box 144, Folder 51)
    - Bylaws, 1995, 2001 (Box 144, Folder 52)
    - Officers and Leadership Information, 1999-2000 (Box 144, Folder 53)
    - Website development, Listserv Transition, 2002, 2004 (Box 144, Folder 54)
    - Elections, 2004 (Box 144, Folder 55)
    - Correspondence, Newsletters, 1978, 1998-2000 (Box 144, Folder 56)
    - Division meeting details, Undated (Box 144, Folder 57)
    - Annual Report, 1982, 1985 (Box 144, Folder 58)
    - Officers and Leadership Information, 1982, 1999 (Box 144, Folder 59)
    - Division Performance, 1998 (Box 144, Folder 60)
  - Divisions Council, APA - Documents
    - Division Orientation Manual, 1997 (Box 145, Folder 1)
    - AICP Membership documents, 1998-1999 (Box 145, Folder 2)
    - Division Orientation Manual, 2000 (Box 145, Folder 3)
    - Planners' Communications Guide - Part I (Sections 1-7), 2006 (Box 145, Folder 4)
    - Planners' Communications Guide - Part II (Sections 8-10), 2006 (Box 145, Folder 5)
    - APA Brand Guidelines, 2007 (Box 145, Folder 6)
    - AICP Exam Prep 2.0 Study Notes with CD (2 copies), 2009 (Box 145, Folder 7)
    - Bank Documents, 2004-2010 (Box 145, Folder 8)
    - Divisions Council Financial Record, 2004-2007 (Box 145, Folder 9)
    - Divisions Council Financial Record, 2008-2010 (Box 145, Folder 10)
    - APA Divisions Council Budget, 2005-2009 (Box 145, Folder 11)
    - APA Chapters - New Mexico, 2000, 2001 (Box 145, Folder 12)
      Proposal for reforming Planning and Land Use Laws
    - Grants
      - Division's Council Grants documents, 1998, 1999, 2003 (Box 145, Folder 13)
      - Division's Council Grants documents, 1999 (Box 145, Folder 14)
      - Planning & Law Division, 2005 (Box 145, Folder 15)
      - General Information, 2005 (Box 145, Folder 16)
      - Indigenous Planning Division, 2006, 2007 (Box 145, Folder 17)
      - Planning & Women's Division, 2005 (Box 145, Folder 18)
      - IT Division, 2005 (Box 145, Folder 19)
        Best Practices Manual
      - GALIP, 2005-2007 (Box 145, Folder 20)
        Cognitive Dimensions of Queer Space
        Mapping safe neighborhoods
      - 2004 Grants (Box 145, Folder 21)
    - Initiatives - Transportation Planning Division, 2005 (Box 145, Folder 22)
    - Initiatives - Food System Planning Group, 2005 (Box 145, Folder 23)
    - Financial Reports, 1996 (Box 145, Folder 24)
    - City Planning & Management (CPM) Division, APA
      - - Meeting Details, 2003 (Box 145, Folder 25)
      - CPM Division, APA - Annual Report, 1978-1989 (Box 145, Folder 26)
      - CPM Division, APA - Correspondence, 1991-1995 (Box 145, Folder 27)
      - Correspondence, 1994-1996 (Box 145, Folder 28)
      - Bylaws, 1988, 1997 (Box 145, Folder 29)
      - Officers and Leadership Information, 1990, 1996, 2000 (Box 145, Folder 30)
      - Survey, 2005 (Box 145, Folder 31)
      - Top 250 cities, 2003 (Box 145, Folder 32)
      - Survey, 2001 (Box 145, Folder 33)
      - Peer Review, City of Atlanta, 2005 (Box 145, Folder 34)
    - Divisions Council - Bylaws, Miscellaneous documents, 1971-1992 (Box 145, Folder 35)
    - AICP Relations, 1981, 1991 (Box 145, Folder 36)
    - Mailing Permit Documents - IRS Letter, 1980, 1995 (Box 145, Folder 37)
    - Mailing Permit Documents, 1990-1995 (Box 145, Folder 38)
    - Elections - Ballot, 1994 (Box 145, Folder 39)
    - Awards, 1996 (Box 145, Folder 40)
    - Economic Development Division (EDD), APA
      - Bylaws, 1985, 1999, 2002 (Box 145, Folder 41)
      - Printing Contract, 2002 (Box 145, Folder 42)
      - Annual Report, 1982, 1991, 1995 (Box 145, Folder 43)
      - Officers and Leadership Information, 2000 (Box 145, Folder 44)
      - Newsletters, 2002 (Box 145, Folder 45)
      - Correspondence, 1996-2000 (Box 145, Folder 46)
      - Elections, 2000-2002 (Box 145, Folder 47)
    - Environmental, Natural Resources & Energy (ENRE) Division, APA
      - Bylaws, 1999 (Box 145, Folder 48)
      - Division Performance, 1998-1999 (Box 145, Folder 49)
      - Officers and Leadership Information, 2000, 2001 (Box 145, Folder 50)
      - Membership Directory, 1996 (Box 145, Folder 51)
      - Annual Reports, 1980-1993 (Box 145, Folder 52)
      - Division Accounts, 1997-1998 (Box 145, Folder 53)
      - Correspondence, 1996-2001, 2007 (Box 145, Folder 54)
    - Proposed Specialisation certification letter, 1999 (Box 146, Folder 1)
    - Strategic Planning documents, 1999 (Box 146, Folder 2)
    - Divisions' Performance Reports, 1999 (Box 146, Folder 3)
    - Membership numbers history, 1983-1997 (Box 146, Folder 4)
    - Tracking Forms, 'Ticklers', etc., 1996 (Box 146, Folder 5)
    - Work Schedule, 1996, Undated (Box 146, Folder 6)
    - Fellowships and Scholarships, 1996 (Box 146, Folder 7)
    - Issues - Tribal Division, AICP Members, 1996 (Box 146, Folder 8)
    - Executive Committee, 1996 (Box 146, Folder 9)
    - Awards, 1996, 1999 (Box 146, Folder 10)
    - Assessments History, 1991-1996 (Box 146, Folder 11)
    - Divisions Financial Statements, 1987, 1994 (Box 146, Folder 12)
    - Quarterly Report Spreadsheet - Transportation Planning Division, 1994; FD-38 (Box 146, Folder 12)
    - Newsletters - 'DC Notes', 1990-1995 (Box 146, Folder 13)
    - Bylaws, 1981 (Box 146, Folder 14)
    - Task Force Report, 1984 (Box 146, Folder 15)
    - Strategic Plan, 1994 (Box 146, Folder 16)
    - Division Orientation Manual, 1996 (Box 146, Folder 17)
    - National Association of County Planners documents, 2005 (Box 146, Folder 18)
    - County Planning - Proposed Division, 2005-2006 (Box 146, Folder 19)
    - County Planning Division - Proposal, 2007 (Box 146, Folder 20)
- Paul Farmer Files
  - Chapters
    - Alabama, 2002 (Box 146, Folder 21)
    - California (Box 146, Folder 22-43)
      - Awards, 2002 (Box 146, Folder 22)
      - CCAPA Conference documents: Catalogs, Brochures,etc., 2002 (Box 146, Folder 23)
      - CCAPA Conference documents: Agendas, Brochures,etc., 2002 (Box 146, Folder 24)
      - CCAPA Conference: San Diego, 2002 (Box 146, Folder 25)
      - Meeting agendas, 2002 (Box 146, Folder 26)
      - Action Reports, Programs, Surveys, 2002-2003 (Box 146, Folder 27)
      - Newsletters, 2002-2003 (Box 146, Folder 28)
      - California planning public information, 2003; DVD-1226 (Box 146, Folder 29)
      - 'Visualize', Architectural and Engineering Visualization, Undated; DVD-1227 (Box 146, Folder 30)
      - CCAPA Conference documents: Budgets, Correspondence, Newsletters,etc., 2003-2007 (Box 146, Folder 31)
      - California conference documents, 2006 (Box 146, Folder 32)
      - Guide to preparation of Housing Elements, 2006 (Box 146, Folder 33)
      - Housing Element Information folder, 2006 (Box 146, Folder 34)
      - Programs, 2006 (Box 146, Folder 35)
      - Countywide Plan 2006 supporting document (Box 146, Folder 36)
      - Conference brochures, flyers, 2006, 2007 (Box 146, Folder 37)
      - CCAPA Board Roster, 2006 (Box 146, Folder 38)
      - California Conference - Brochures, Flyers, 2006 (Box 146, Folder 39)
      - Employment, 2006 (Box 146, Folder 40)
      - Correspondence, 2006 (Box 146, Folder 41)
      - UCLA Extension Fall Seminar schedule, 2003 (Box 146, Folder 42)
      - Employment, 2003 (Box 146, Folder 43)
    - Colorado - Report: 'The Colorado Index', 2001 (Box 146, Folder 44)
    - Colorado - Brochures, Programs, Flyers, 'The Colorado Smart Growth Scorecard', 2002 (Box 146, Folder 45)
    - Colorado - Zoning Analyst for ArcGIS, 2002; DVD-1228 (Box 146, Folder 45)
    - Colorado - Flyers, Brochures, Programs, etc., 2002 (Box 146, Folder 46)
    - Chicago Metro Section, 2003-2004 (Box 146, Folder 47)
    - Florida - 2003 Conference printed materials (Box 146, Folder 48)
    - Florida - Report 'Waterwise':Xeriscape, 2003 (Box 146, Folder 49)
    - Florida - 2006 Conference correspondence (Box 146, Folder 50)
    - Illinois, 2002 (Box 146, Folder 51)
    - Louisiana, 2001 (Box 146, Folder 52)
    - Michigan - Annual report, Correspondence, Conference Report, 2001-2004 (Folder 53)
    - Missouri, 2004 (Box 146, Folder 54)
    - National Capital Area, 2001 (Box 146, Folder 55)
    - New Jersey, 2007 (Box 146, Folder 56)
    - New York Metro, 2002-2003 (Box 146, Folder 57)
    - New York Upstate, 2003-2007 (Box 146, Folder 58)
    - Pennsylvania, 2003-2004 (Box 146, Folder 59)
    - Oregon, 2002-2004 (Box 146, Folder 60)
    - Rhode Island, 2002 (Box 146, Folder 61)
    - South Carolina, 2003-2004 (Box 146, Folder 62)
    - Tennessee, 2002 (Box 146, Folder 63)
    - Texas - Correspondence, Flyers, Brochures, Maps etc., 2002 (Box 146, Folder 64)
    - Utah, 2002 (Box 146, Folder 65)
    - Virginia, 1987, 2002 (Box 146, Folder 66)
  - Divisions
    - Intergovernmental Affairs, 2001 (Box 147, Folder 1)
    - City Planning and Management, 2003, 2006 (Box 147, Folder 2)
      Offers of assistance, Program and Budget
    - International, 2004 (Box 147, Folder 3)
    - Planning & Black Community, 2002-2007 (Box 147, Folder 4)
      Correspondence, Newsletter, Budget etc.
    - Planning & Law, 2002 (Box 147, Folder 5)
      Correspondence
    - Small Town & Rural Planning, 2005, 2007 (Box 147, Folder 6)
      Correspondence, Newsletter
    - Urban Design and Preservation, 2007 (Box 147, Folder 7)
      Conference Call details
  - AICP
    - Dues History, 1999-2002 (Box 147, Folder 8)
    - APA-AICP Measures of progress, 2000 (Box 147, Folder 9)
    - Awards, 2001 (Box 147, Folder 10)
    - College of Fellows, FAICP Guidelines, Correspondence, 2001-2008 (Box 147, Folder 11)
    - Planning Landmark, 2002 (Box 147, Folder 12)
    - Commission: correspondence, reports, meeting minutes, 2002 (Box 147, Folder 13)
    - Commission: correspondence, task force documents, agenda, printed materials, 2002-2003 (Box 147, Folder 14)
    - AICP/ACSP Planning Task Force, 2002-2003 (Box 147, Folder 15)
    - Exam committee documents, 2002-2004 (Box 147, Folder 16)
    - Benefits, 2003 (Box 147, Folder 17)
    - Ex-member correspondence, 2003 (Box 147, Folder 18)
    - Training, 2005 (Box 147, Folder 19)
    - Executive recruiters, 2005, 2006 (Box 147, Folder 20)
    - Exam proposal revised, Prometrics, 2006 (Box 147, Folder 21)
    - Exam Services, Exam Appeals, 2006, 2007 (Box 147, Folder 22)
    - Symposium invitation letters, 2007 (Box 147, Folder 23)
    - Continuing professional development web pages - edits, drafts, 2007 (Box 147, Folder 24)
    - Committees, 2007 (Box 147, Folder 25)
    - Manager resumes, 2007 (Box 147, Folder 26)
    - Professional development officers memo, 2007 (Box 147, Folder 27)
    - STaR division certification maintenance subsidy program, 2007 (Box 147, Folder 28)
    - Transportation Certification, 2008 (Box 147, Folder 29)
  - APA
    - Burnham conference centre, 2005 (Box 147, Folder 30)
    - Centennial, 2005, 2006 (Box 147, Folder 31)
    - Awards task force, 2001 (Box 147, Folder 32)
    - Awards program, 2002, Undated (Box 147, Folder 33)
    - Awards program 2004 (Box 147, Folder 34)
    - Awards program 2006 (Box 147, Folder 35)
      Meeting summary, Newsletters, Flyers
    - HUD, Plan, Current Topic, Singles, Doubles, Undated; CD-2218 (Box 147, Folder 35)
    - Awards program 2006 (Box 147, Folder 36)
      Outstanding planning award for a plan
    - Awards program 2006 (Box 147, Folder 37)
      a. Current topic award 'Housing choice and affordability',
      b. The HUD Secretary's 'Opportunity and empowerment Award'
    - Awards program 2006 (Box 147, Folder 38)
      Paul Davidoff national award for Social Advocacy
    - Awards program 2006 (Box 147, Folder 39)
      Meeting agendas, Correspondence
    - AZ Planning Association 501(c)(3) issues, 2006 (Box 147, Folder 40)
    - Amicus Curiae Committee: Rapanos et. al vs. USA, 2001, 2003, 2004 (Box 147, Folder 41)
    - Amicus Curiae Committee documents, 2003 (Box 147, Folder 42)
    - Amicus Curiae Committee: Norwood vs. Horney, 2006 (Box 147, Folder 43)
    - Amicus Curiae Committee calls, 2007 (Box 147, Folder 44-45)
    - Audio/Web conferences: Tapes for 2007-2008 (Box 147, Folder 46)
    - Awards program jury meeting, 2008 (Box 147, Folder 47)
    - Affiliates program, 2009 (Box 147, Folder 48)
    - Divisions Performances, 2009 (Box 147, Folder 49)
    - Directors Meeting, 2002 (Box 147, Folder 50)
    - Communications Plans, 2002-2003, 2004, 2007 (Box 147, Folder 51)
    - Division Council, 2003 (Box 147, Folder 52)
    - APA History, 2003 (Box 147, Folder 53)
    - Governance Committee documents, 2004 (Box 147, Folder 54)
    - Development plan budget committee documents, 2004 (Box 147, Folder 55)
    - Development plan budget committee - Conference calls, 2007 (Box 147, Folder 56)
    - FEMA Contract, 2005 (Box 147, Folder 57)
    - Directors network, 2005 (Box 147, Folder 58)
    - Holiday cards, Cards list, 2006, 2007 (Box 147, Folder 59)
    - Centennial Planning - Brainstorm Meeting, 2007 (Box 147, Folder 60)
    - 30th Anniversary Gala (WTS), 2007 (Box 147, Folder 61)
    - Job Applications, 2007, 2008 (Box 147, Folder 62)
    - Consultation for city of Greensboro, 2011 (Box 147, Folder 63)
    - GPinA: Biennial, 2013 (Box 147, Folder 64)
    - IT Division documents, Undated (Box 147, Folder 65)
    - Departments
      - Marketing, 2000-2002 (Box 147, Folder 66)
      - Memberships, 2001-2002 (Box 147, Folder 67)
      - Public Affairs, 2002 (Box 147, Folder 68)
      - Leadership, 2002 (Box 147, Folder 69)
      - Web, 2002 (Box 147, Folder 70)
      - Research, 2002 (Box 147, Folder 71)
      - Publications, 2002 (Box 147, Folder 72)
      - Policy and Outreach, 2002 (Box 147, Folder 73)
      - AICP, 2002-2003 (Box 147, Folder 74)
      - Education, 2002-2003 (Box 147, Folder 75)
      - Planning Advisory Services (PAS), 2002-2003 (Box 147, Folder 76)
      - Government Affairs, 2003 (Box 147, Folder 77)
      - Marketing - Zoning Practice (ZP), 2004 (Box 147, Folder 78)
        Legal size folder
      - Marketing - Planning & Environmental Law (PEL), 2004 (Box 147, Folder 79)
    - Alan Voorhees (FAICP), 2003 (Box 147, Folder 80)
      Obituary, APA Journal article
    - APA Foundation
      - Donations for Katrina Relief, 2005 (Box 148, Folder 1)
      - Planning Foundation Board Conference Call, 2005 (Box 148, Folder 2)
      - Visioning and Development Planning Guidebook, 2005 (Box 148, Folder 3)
      - Board Meeting Minutes, 2005 (Box 148, Folder 4)
      - Examples, 2005-2010 (Box 148, Folder 5)
    - China Initiative
      - Report - DISP 151 - Sustainable Urban & Regional Development in China, 2002 (Box 148, Folder 6)
      - Correspondence, Newspaper cuttings, Reports etc., 2002, 2003 (Box 148, Folder 7)
      - Correspondence, Schedules, Programs, Proposals etc., 2002-2004 (Box 148, Folder 8)
      - China (Meck), 2004 (Box 148, Folder 9)
      - Correspondence, Brochures, Programs etc., 2002-2005 (Box 148, Folder 10)
      - Visits to the US documents, brochure on Jiangsu, China, 2005 (Box 148, Folder 11)
      - Report - Promoting U.S. Planning Services in China, 2005 (Box 148, Folder 12)
      - Scholarship Applications for China Study Tour, 2007 (Box 148, Folder 13-14)
      - Application for Scholarship - APA's China Study Tour, 2007 (Box 148, Folder 15)
      - Library, email, 2001 (Box 148, Folder 16)
      - Leadership meetings, 2001-2003 (Box 148, Folder 17)
      - Legal & Policy Committee Conference Call, Related documents, 2006 (Box 148, Folder 18)
      - Legal & Policy Committee Conference Call, 2007 (Box 148, Folder 19)
      - Job Applicants, Jobs online, 2009, 2010 (Box 148, Folder 20)
      - Preliminary Membership Survey, 2006 (Box 148, Folder 21-23)
      - National Centers for Planning meeting, 2008 (Box 148, Folder 24)
      - National planning conference cities (venues), 1909-2020 (Box 148, Folder 25)
      - Planners Bookservice, 2003, 2005 (Box 148, Folder 26)
      - Planners Press - "Good news about takings", 2005 (Box 148, Folder 27)
      - Planners Press - "Overlooked America", 2008 (Box 148, Folder 28)
      - Planners Press Meetings documents, 2002-2009 (Box 148, Folder 29-41)
      - Planning Research Registry, 2008 (Box 148, Folder 42)
      - Policy Publication, Undated (Box 148, Folder 43)
    - Practicing Planner Survey Questionnaire, 2009 (Box 149, Folder 1)
    - Research Center / Planning & Community Health, 2007 (Box 149, Folder 2)
    - Regional contacts / NV Chapter - A. Freund, 2005 (Box 149, Folder 3)
    - Regional contacts / CA Chapter - J. Ram, 2005 (Box 149, Folder 4)
    - Salary Survey, 2006 (Box 149, Folder 5)
    - Super Topic: Green Communities, 2007 (Box 149, Folder 6)
      Correspondence, Report - 'Conservation Thresholds for Planners'
    - Super Topic: Green Communities, 2007 (Box 149, Folder 7)
      Report - 'Lasting landscapes: reflections on the role of Conservation Science in Land Use Planning'
    - WEB: Jobs online, 2006 (Box 149, Folder 8)
    - Web Redesign: Diagnostic tools, 2007 (Box 149, Folder 9)
  - Alphabetical File
    - American Bar Association (ABA)- Member booklet, 2004-2006 (Box 149, Folder 10)
    - Active Matter, 2002 (Box 149, Folder 11)
    - Affordable Housing, 2002, 2003 (Box 149, Folder 12)
    - American Express, 2001, 2002 (Box 149, Folder 13)
    - American Farmland Trust (AFT)- Printed materials, 2001 (Box 149, Folder 14-18)
    - APCO, 2005 (Box 149, Folder 19)
    - American Public Transportation Association, 2002-2003 (Box 149, Folder 20)
    - Arizona Board of Regents, 2003 (Box 149, Folder 21)
    - ASIS International, 2005 (Box 149, Folder 22)
    - Associated Black Charities, 2002 (Box 149, Folder 23)
    - Arizona State University, 2006 (Box 149, Folder 24)
    - American Society of Landscape Architects (ASLA), 2005, 2009 (Box 149, Folder 25)
    - Awards, 2002, 2003 (Box 149, Folder 26)
    - City of Baltimore, 2007 (Box 149, Folder 27)
    - Banta Publications, 2003 (Box 149, Folder 28)
      Report - 'Analysis of the "Comdisco" annexation agreement'
    - Kingdom of Bhutan, correspondence, 2006 (Box 149, Folder 29)
    - Branding, 2007 (Box 149, Folder 30)
    - Brick Industry Association, 2002 (Box 149, Folder 31)
    - Building Architects (Torchia), Undated (Box 149, Folder 32)
    - Building codes, 2002 (Box 149, Folder 33)
    - The Brookings Institute Publications (Center on Urban & Metropolitan Planning, 2001-2004 (Box 149, Folder 34-38)
    - Cal Poly - Urban & Regional Planning Department, 2007 (Box 149, Folder 39)
    - CB- Richard Ellis documents, 2008-2010 (Box 149, Folder 40)
    - Chapters, 2002 (Box 149, Folder 41)
    - Chapter CPC - Executive committee, 2004 (Box 149, Folder 42)
    - CDs- Land Use, Ottawa, 2002, Undated; CD-2313 - 2314 (Box 149, Folder 43)
    - CDs- Opportunities on the horizon,Ppts, Undated; CD-2219, CD- 2310-2312 (Box 149, Folder 44)
    - Chauncey Group international contract, 2002-2005 (Box 149, Folder 45)
    - City of Chicago, 2002-2003 (Box 149, Folder 46)
    - Charles Causier Scholarship, 2002 (Box 149, Folder 46)
    - China- Nanjing city development strategy, 2003 (Box 149, Folder 47)
    - Cincinnati, 2002, 2003 (Box 149, Folder 48)
    - City Parks Forum, 2002 (Box 149, Folder 49)
    - Cleveland State University, 1994, 2006 (Box 149, Folder 50)
    - CLIDE Awards, Jury Materials, CD, 2005 (Box 149, Folder 51)
      North Central Texas Council of Governments
    - 2005 CLIDE Awards Program, CD-2315 (Box 149, Folder 52)
    - Committee for Economic Development, 2004 (Box 149, Folder 53)
    - Easley Commission, 2003 (Box 149, Folder 54)
    - Comprehensive plan for task force, 2003 (Box 150, Folder 1)
    - Congress for New Urbanism, 2002-2004 (Box 150, Folder 2)
    - Consultants, 1990, 2001-2002 (Box 150, Folder 3)
    - Conservation Fund Roundtable - Fax, Reports, 2006 (Box 150, Folder 4)
    - Courtesy Copies (APA Publications), 2001 (Box 150, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence Received - Strange letters, 2008 (Box 150, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence - Customer Service Letters to Paul Farmer, 2011 (Box 150, Folder 7)
    - College of Urban Planning and Public Affairs (CUPPA) - University of Illinois Chicago, 2004 (Box 150, Folder 8)
    - Czech Republic, 2002 (Box 150, Folder 9)
    - Denver, 2003 (Box 150, Folder 10)
    - Department of Transportation (DOT), 2004 (Box 150, Folder 11)
    - Downtown Idea Exchange - Newsletters, 201, 2002 (Box 150, Folder 12)
    - Downtown Kendall Urban Center District, Undated (Box 150, Folder 13)
    - Daniel Drummond, 2003, 2005 (Box 150, Folder 14)
    - Dupont Hotel Contracts, 2011 (Box 150, Folder 15)
    - Edmond Bacon - Letter regarding 'ruined Penn's Landing controversy', 2002 (Box 150, Folder 16)
    - Education - Correspondence, Programs, 2002, 2003 (Box 150, Folder 17)
    - Egon Zehnder International, 2003 (Box 150, Folder 18)
    - Elections - Violations, 2004 (Box 150, Folder 19)
    - Executive Director - Bio and Photos, 2002 (Box 150, Folder 20)
    - Executive Search Inc. - Information, 2007 (Box 150, Folder 21)
    - City of Eugene - Newsletter, 2003 (Box 150, Folder 22)
    - Environmental Protection Agency, 2004 (Box 150, Folder 23)
    - Environmental Planning, 2001 (Box 150, Folder 24)
    - Enterprise Community Partners, 2007 (Box 150, Folder 25)
    - Manuscript: 'Energy in America' - pgs 1-260, 2008 (Box 150, Folder 26)
    - Manuscript: 'Energy in America' - pgs 261-402, 2008 (Box 150, Folder 27)
    - FAICP - Mentoring Recommendation, 2000 (Box 150, Folder 28)
    - FAICP - Fellows Nomination, 2002 (Box 150, Folder 29)
    - Federal Highway Administration - Printed materials, 2000 (Box 150, Folder 30)
    - Federal Highway Administration - Printed materials, 2002, 2003 (Box 150, Folder 31)
    - Film Project, 2002-2003 (Box 150, Folder 32)
    - Forest Service, 2002 (Box 150, Folder 33)
    - Foundations Documents, 2002-2004 (Box 150, Folder 34)
    - California Planning Foundation, 2005 (Box 150, Folder 35)
    - Daniel J. Curtin Fund, 2007 (Box 150, Folder 36)
    - Ed Bacon Foundation, Undated (Box 150, Folder 37)
    - Enterprise Foundation, 2003, 2005 (Box 150, Folder 38)
    - Fannie Mae Foundation, 2001-2004 (Box 150, Folder 39)
    - Food Foundation, 2003 (Box 150, Folder 40)
    - Graham Pelting, 2003 (Box 150, Folder 41)
    - KnowledgeWorks, 2005 (Box 150, Folder 42)
    - Landscape Architecture Foundation, 2002 (Box 150, Folder 43)
    - Lincoln Institute, 2005 (Box 150, Folder 44)
    - Milton & Rose D. Friedman, Undated (Box 150, Folder 45)
    - Orton Foundation, 2002 (Box 150, Folder 46)
    - Planning Foundation, 2003 (Box 150, Folder 47)
    - Robert Wood Johnson, 1997, 2001-2003 (Box 150, Folder 48)
    - Rockefeller: Jane Jacobs Jury, 2008 (Box 150, Folder 49)
    - Signage Foundation: Correspondence, Judgement, 2001-2002, 2007 (Box 150, Folder 50)
    - Surdna Foundation Inc.: NYC Meeting Details, 2009 (Box 150, Folder 51)
    - William W. Bowdy Fund, 2002 (Box 150, Folder 52)
    - William & Flora Hewlett Foundation, 2003 (Box 150, Folder 53)
    - Donor Letters, 2001 (Box 150, Folder 54)
    - Fraser Trust, 2001 (Box 150, Folder 55)
    - Freedom Museum (McCormick Trust), 2006 (Box 150, Folder 56)
    - Frielich Book - Contract & Promotion, 2008 (Box 150, Folder 57)
    - "From Washington", 2004 (Box 150, Folder 58)
    - Fundraiser, 2001 (Box 150, Folder 59)